Push, Mrs. Fry. You're almost there.
You can do it, honey.
Squeeze one out for America.
Hey, keep it down! It's the ninth inning!
Here's the 0-2 pitch to Claypool.
He's taking all the way
for a called strike three.
Swing the bat, you bum!
It's a boy. And look at that red hair!
You saying my son is a commie?
And Grody leans into the pitch.
It hits him! The Mets win!
This is the happiest day of my life!
Here's your baby, ma'am.
Yeah, okay, thanks.
So, what should we name him?
Eh, you pick. I picked dinner last night.
Well, I was thinking of Philip,
after those screwdrivers.
That's a fantastic idea.
More morphine, please.
Look, Yancy, it's
your baby brother Philip.
I wanna be named Philip!
Me Philip! Me Philip!
Son, your name is Yancy,
just like me and my grandfather,
and so on,
all the way back to minuteman Yancy Fry,
who blasted commies
in the American Revolution.
Philip, until I find
a suitable model of an ICBM,
you'll have to make do
learning to fear this toy spacecraft.
Mine! Mine!
Come on!
Baby needs a new pair of shoes!
To hell with your spoiled baby.
I need those shoes!
And it's a dead heat!
They're checking the electron microscope.
And the winner is
number three in a quantum finish!
No fair!
You changed the outcome by measuring it!
How'd you do, Fry?
I'll tell you when my horse finishes.
Bad.
In today's field,
we own four horses and two jockeys.
We just put our best jockey
out to stud, Amy.
He's perfect for you.
Hey, baby, ever do it in a suitcase?
Ooh, look! It's the centaur race!
Ow! Oh!
Come on, come on!
Hey, Leela, how about a kiss
for good luck?
I meant tongue luck.
Ow! Ow!
And the winner is
number four, Steven!
I am so unlucky.
I've run over black cats
that were luckier than me.
Get your piping hot horse burgers,
horse fries, horse cakes and shakes.
We got tongue
straight from the horse's mouth.
- Hmm...
- It all sounds good.
All our horses are 100% horse-fed
for that double-horse, juiced-in goodness.
I'll have the cholesterol-free omelet
with Horse Beaters.
And you, sir? How can I horse you?
I'll have a horse Coke.
Horse Pepsi okay?
Nay.
Hey, what are you doing?
This.
Dear horse god,
I know I don't usually pray to you.
Sometimes I doubt you even exist.
But if you're willing to grant me luck,
please stamp your hoof once.
Come on, number six! Move it!
Don't do that! What are you...
Man, it's contagious.
And the winner is Harry Trotter
by the entire racetrack.
Yahoo!
That'll teach those other horses
to take drugs.
That's it!
You can only take my money
for so long before you take it all,
and I say enough!
I've got $1 left,
and this one I'm holding on to.
Oh, no, you don't.
I may not know much about horses,
but I know a lot
about doing anything for $1.
If you think bad luck can defeat me,
then you don't know my name is Philip J...
Phew!
That is one unlucky guy.
Kareem's got the skyhook,
but Philip J. Fry's got the space-hook.
Yancy drives.
He goes up with his patented space-hook.
Hey! That's my patented space-hook.
You stole it.
You're not the president of it.
Holy camoly!
A seven-leaf clover!
I'm dying of old age!
Game over! Phil wins!
Yancy's fans are stunned!
There'll be no celebration
at the Yancydome!
Lucky.
Well, someone's in a good mode.
Let's just say I lucked out at the track.
Also, I rigged one race.
I'd have won
a lot of money, too,
if I still had my lucky seven-leaf clover.
Plus, I'd still have my hair.
I got your page, Mr. Fry.
Your new hair is ready.
So, whatever happened
to this seven-leaf clover?
I hid it in a secret hiding place
whose location I never told anyone.
Not even Scruffy.
So the clover is still
in the hiding place, maybe?
Hey, yeah, maybe it is still there,
underground in the ruins of Old New York,
helping some ant defeat another ant.
Or helping some piece of dirt
turn its luck around.
Dirt doesn't need luck.
I'm going down there
to get my clover back.
Some of the tunnels have metal bars,
so I'll need someone
who's good at bending.
- Leela, how about you?
- Sure, I'll do it.
Like hell you will!
Bending is my middle name.
- It is?
- Yeah.
My full name is Bender Bending Rodriguez.
Here's the entrance.
From this moment on,
I declare my bad luck officially over.
He was fun.
Well, if we get bored
looking for the clover,
I've got Tetris on this thing.
Look, up ahead.
Old New York.
The city that inspired
a casino in Las Vegas.
Wow, we've got Manhattan all to ourselves.
I can finally do all the crazy stuff
I always dreamed of doing.
Howard Stern is overrated!
Oh... Oops!
New York is so burned!
Remember when Mayor Giuliani
cracked down on jaywalking?
- No.
- Well, Rudy, how do you like this action?
Ooh!
As you know,
the big break-dance battle is Saturday.
So if we want to win
those Jam Master Jay
autographed parachute pants,
our crew has to pop,
lock and bust the freshest.
Noticeably F.A.T., drop us a beat.
- Name?
- Cosmic F.
- Style?
- Outer space.
Special moves?
The moonwalk.
The robot.
The Zero G.
- Name?
- Cosmic Y.
Style?
Uh... Deep space.
"Deep space"?
Special moves?
- The space walk.
- Hey!
- The robot.
- The robot? That's similar to mine!
The Zero G.
What are you doing?
You totally ripped off my routine.
You calling me a biter?
Why do you always have to steal
everything from me, Yancy?
Find your own life and live it.
Stop illin'. Word.
Well, I'd like to see you
try to steal this!
The septuple head spin.
He's just scratching.
No one's ever done more than a quadruple.
Oh, yeah?
Noticeably F.A.T., rewind the tape.
Crazy sucker.
Phil, you're hype!
That was ice-cold, bro.
Fry, if I ever see you try
anything that crazy again,
this crew might just have
some new parachute pants!
Stop hogging the clover!
Ow!
All right, team.
Let's go find that clover.
Which way to your house?
The sign says we're at 71st Street.
71st Street?
Hmm. Never heard of it.
Downtown could be in any direction.
No sweat.
We'll just take a spin on the B train.
Ooh!
That feels funny.
This is
the Brooklyn-bound B train,
making local stops
at wherever the hell I feel like.
Watch for the closing doors.
Wake up, buddy. End of the line.
Gosh, my old neighborhood.
Oh!
That's the bench
where I found some shirts!
That fire hydrant,
in the summer, we'd light on fire.
On that corner,
some guy with a bushy beard
handed out a socialist newsletter.
Was it poorly xeroxed?
You better believe it.
The old comedians were right.
This place is a lot different from LA.
Pardon me. Did I overhear you say
you used to live here?
- That's right.
- Did you know Andy Goldman?
Yeah. He was my neighbor. Why?
I mutated from him!
Get outta here!
What's Andy up to these days?
The short answer is, I'm teaching.
- He seemed nice.
- Sure, when he's sober.
Holy camoly!
The house I grew up in!
It's still there!
Man, Father Time
really took a bat to this place.
That stupid clover
is a worthless piece of garbage!
Give it, give it, give it!
Mom! Help!
Yes!
Mom, Yancy's trying to steal my clover.
Yancy, stealing is wrong.
- I'm gonna pile-drive you!
- Stop it!
You're dead meat!
What's happening up there?
Did Kremlin Joe let fly with the nukes?
Not yet, Commander.
Yancy's just trying
to steal my stuff, as usual.
Well, he'd better keep
his hands off these bananas.
Gonna need them when the radiation
turns us all into monkeys.
The Ronco Record Vault.
Yancy will never get his hands on you
in here, or my money back.
Ah! The Breakfast Club soundtrack.
Man, I can't wait till I'm old enough
to feel ways about stuff.
Stay safe, clover.
I may need you again someday.
This was the storage room.
My dad spent years
turning it into a bomb shelter.
And yet you guys never had
a single nuclear war.
What a waste.
This is it.
My Ronco Record Vault.
I still remember the combination.
Three.
It's stuck.
The Achilles' heel of the Ronco design
is its structural resonance frequency.
Allow me.
There we go.
Here it is.
The Breakfast Club soundtrack.
You mean breakfast club sandwich.
I hid my seven-leaf clover
in this very record jacket,
so my brother Yancy wouldn't get it.
Here goes.
It's gone!
The whole place has been cleaned out!
Yancy stole my clover. That thief!
How do you know it didn't disintegrate?
Everything else in here held up okay.
Except Sports by Huey Lewis.
I don't know why my brother
hated me so much.
Oh... Brothers always fight.
I'm sure deep down he loved you.
He just never got a chance to say it
before you got frozen.
You think?
'Cause I always kind of wished that...
Who is that godlike figure?
It's my brother, Yancy!
And there, in his lapel,
my seven-leaf clover!
I knew he stole it!
Hold the phone.
If that's Yancy, why does
the inscription say "Philip J. Fry"?
Wait a second. That's my name.
Good Lord!
He ditched his goofy name and stole mine!
Apparently, this brave Adonis,
this Cadillac of men,
was the "first person on Mars."
First person on Mars?
I should have been
the first person on Mars!
He stole my clover,
he stole my name, and he stole my life.
And now he broke my hand.
His legend lives on.
So you opened the record vault,
and the clover was gone?
Yep. Nothing in there
but all the best music of the 1980s
in one amazing collection.
Survivor, Pat Benatar, the Scorpions.
The list goes on.
That clover helped my rat fink brother
steal my dream of going into space.
Now I'll never get there.
You went there this morning for doughnuts.
"First person on Mars."
Oh! So your brother
was that Philip J. Fry.
I'm Philip J. Fry!
He stole my name after I got frozen.
Shut up, friends.
My Internet browser
heard us saying the word "Fry,"
and it found a movie
about Philip J. Fry for us.
It also opened my calendar to Friday
and ordered me some French fries.
Philip J. Fry,
astronaut, philanthropist, entrepreneur,
was a great man truly worthy of narration.
Fry was the first man on Mars,
a feat that has never since been equaled.
That should've been me!
The ever-lucky Fry
made his fortune after striking oil
in the bathroom of the mansion
he had won in a lottery.
That's my clover! Yancy stole it.
After a whirlwind fling
with Icelandic supermodel Njord,
Fry scored a string of top-10 hits
with his rock band Leaf Seven,
known for their hypnotic rhythms,
driving bass lines and memorable hooks.
That's what I'm known for!
Phil came in, right?
He strummed out this tune, yeah?
And I said, "That's a number-one record."
Today,
Fry spends most of his time
in his grave
at Orbiting Meadows National Cemetery,
buried with the trademark
seven-leaf clover
that will bring him luck in the next life,
perhaps, some Egyptians believe.
So that's where my clover is.
Hey, is that orbiting cemetery near here?
It will be in a couple hours.
Good. Leela, Bender,
we're going grave robbing.
I'll get my kit!
Thanks for lending me your tux, Dad.
It'll be perfect for my wedding.
Yancy, that tux got me
through 'Nam in style.
I just wish your brother
was still around to see this.
I'll never forget the day
Philip disappeared.
Wisconsin won the Rose Bowl, 17-9.
Oh, I miss him.
Ooh, that reminds me. I was thinking
I'd rummage through Phil's records
- for something to play at the wedding.
- Have a look downstairs.
Your brother may be missing,
but his crap sure isn't.
Huh. Breakfast Club.
This'll clear out the room
at the end of the reception.
They buried your brother
in the "World Heroes" section?
I'm impressed.
I should be the one in that grave!
Hmm. We lost Bender.
There.
Now no one will be able to say
I don't own John Larroquette's spine.
Aha! My brother's grave.
Oh, it's all lies, every word of it.
He wasn't original. He wasn't a Martian.
He wasn't Philip Fry.
And since when is he a "The"?
You're twice the "The" he ever was.
It's clovering time.
So, had any ideas for names, Yancy?
Mmm, I'm sort of thinking of one.
Daddy has a present for you today.
Do you know what it is?
It's a lucky clover that can help you
be successful, whatever you do.
Even break dancing.
And it once belonged
to someone very special.
I know what name
you want to give him, Yancy.
- It's okay.
- Really?
Son,
I'm naming you Philip J. Fry,
in honor of my little brother,
who I miss every day.
I love you, Philip,
and I always will.
Pay dirt! I got the clover,
plus his wedding ring.
Sorry, ladies, I'm taken.
Hey, Fry, you want me
to smack the corpse up a little?
Uh, Bender,
I think Fry needs a moment alone.
All right. Grab a shovel.
I'm only one skull short
of a Mouseketeer reunion.
Don't you
Forget about me
Don't, don't, don't, don't
Don't you
Forget about me
Will you recognize me
Call my name or walk on by